spotrac.com 2018-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Spotrac.com

All player, team, and league information found on spotrac.com is for informational purposes only and is not guaranteed for accuracy by spotrac.com. We do our very best to keep our site properly updated. If you should find information within the site that you do not feel is accurate please email the update at [info@spotrac.com](mailto:info@spotrac.com). 

We take privacy of our users very seriously. This privacy policy explains what information we will collect about you, how we will use it and the steps we will take to ensure that it is kept secure. 

By using spotrac.com you consent to us to collect and use personal information about you by the terms set out in this policy. We may update this privacy policy from time to time, so please check back here periodically.

**Not Affiliated with MLB, NBA, NFL, NHL**  
spotrac.com is not directly or indirectly affiliated, associated or connected in any way to Major League Baseball, the National Basketball Association, the National Football League or the National Hockey League.

 **Use of MLB, NBA, NFL, NHL Logos & Trademarks**  
spotrac.com uses member teams' logos ONLY for educational and news reporting purposes such as displaying the team logos on the splash pages of their respective sport to allow our users a more graphical navigation flow. These logos and other trademarks held by the MLB, NBA, NFL, NHL respectively,  and its members teams are not used in any way for commercial or financial purposes.   
 **  
What Information We Collect  
** We collect information regarding your visit to this site (such as which pages you’ve visited, how often you’ve visited and comments you’ve provided) and the information you supply when subscribing to any portion of this site (such as your name and e-mail address) will be held and securely stored by spotrac.com.

 **How We Will Use Your Information  
** Your information will help us to improve our site and design features that are important to you, our customers.We will also use your information to tell you about any of our new features, products or services that we think might interest you. If you do not wish us to use your information as set out in this paragraph you should email us at [info@spotrac.com](mailto:privacy@spotrac.com).

By supplying us with your information, you have confirmed that you do not consider use of your information in accordance with this privacy policy to be a breach of any rights under all applicable laws, online privacy policies and regulations.

 **How We Will Keep Your Information Secure  
** Safely capturing and storing your information is very important to us. We will use all reasonable measures to safeguard your data but please note: we cannot guarantee that any and all data transmissions over the Internet are completely secure.

**  
Google Vendor Properties**  
spotrac.com uses Google, as a third party vendor, for serving ads and collecting analytics specific to our users. Targeted advertisements. Targeted ads or interest-based offers may be presented to you based on your activities on our webpages, and other websites, and based on the products you currently own. These offers will display as varying product banners presented to you while browsing. We also partner with third parties to manage our advertising on our webpages and other websites. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about such activities in order to provide you with advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests, and to measure advertising effectiveness.

Third-party websites. Our website contains links to third-party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third-party sites. Please read the privacy policy of any website you visit.
